questions = {
    "easy": [
        {
            "question": "Who is the author of the classic science fiction novel 'Dune'?",
            "options": ["Frank Herbert", "Isaac Asimov", "Robert A. Heinlein", "Arthur C. Clarke"],
            "answer": "Frank Herbert"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who wrote the 'Foundation' series, which chronicles the rise and fall of a galactic empire?",
            "options": ["Isaac Asimov", "Frank Herbert", "Robert A. Heinlein", "Arthur C. Clarke"],
            "answer": "Isaac Asimov"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the planet that the novel 'Dune' is set on?",
            "options": ["Arrakis", "Tatooine", "Vulcan", "Pandora"],
            "answer": "Arrakis"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the spaceship in the movie 'Alien'?",
            "options": ["Nostromo", "Sulaco", "Enterprise", "Millennium Falcon"],
            "answer": "Nostromo"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the alien in the movie 'E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial'?",
            "options": ["E.T.", "Groot", "Rocket", "Xenomorph"],
            "answer": "E.T."
        },
        {
            "question": "What do Androids Dream About?",
            "options": ["Electric Sheep", "Electric Penguins", "Electric Eel", "Electric Kettle"],
            "answer": "Electric Sheep"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the tree-like alien in 'Guardians of the Galaxy'?",
            "options": ["Groot", "Rocket", "Drax", "Gamora"],
            "answer": "Groot"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the genetically-engineered raccoon in 'Guardians of the Galaxy'?",
            "options": ["Rocket", "Groot", "Drax", "Gamora"],
            "answer": "Rocket"
        }
    ],
    "medium": [
        {
            "question": "In Ray Bradbury's 'Fahrenheit 451', what is the occupation of the protagonist, Guy Montag?",
            "options": ["Firefighter", "Police Officer", "Journalist", "Writer"],
            "answer": "Firefighter"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the author of 'The War of the Worlds', a novel about a Martian invasion of Earth?",
            "options": ["H.G. Wells", "Jules Verne", "Mary Shelley", "Edgar Rice Burroughs"],
            "answer": "H.G. Wells"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the title of the science fiction novel by Aldous Huxley that portrays a dystopian future society where people are genetically engineered and heavily medicated?",
            "options": ["Brave New World", "1984", "Fahrenheit 451", "The Handmaid's Tale"],
            "answer": "Brave New World"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the author of the science fiction novel 'Ender's Game'?",
            "options": ["Orson Scott Card", "Isaac Asimov", "Robert A. Heinlein", "Frank Herbert"],
            "answer": "Orson Scott Card"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the movie 'Blade Runner', what is the name of the corporation that creates the replicants?",
            "options": ["Tyrell Corporation", "Weyland-Yutani Corporation", "Umbrella Corporation", "InGen Corporation"],
            "answer": "Tyrell Corporation"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the main character in the novel 'Brave New World' by Aldous Huxley?",
            "options": ["Bernard Marx", "Winston Smith", "John Savage", "Mustapha Mond"],
            "answer": "Bernard Marx"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the movie 'The Matrix', what is the name of the main character played by Keanu Reeves?",
            "options": ["Thomas Anderson", "John Wick", "Jack Traven", "Johnny Mnemonic"],
            "answer": "Thomas Anderson"
        }
    ],
    "hard": [
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the sentient planet in the science fiction novel by Stanislaw Lem, which is also the title of the book?",
            "options": ["Solaris", "Lusitania", "Trantor", "Arrakis"],
            "answer": "Solaris"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the sandworms that live on the planet 'Dune'?",
            "options": ["Shai-Hulud", "Krayt Dragon", "Sarlacc", "Sarlacci"],
            "answer": "Shai-Hulud"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the substance that the Spacing Guild requires in order to fold space in the 'Dune' series?",
            "options": ["The Spice Melange", "The Water of Life", "The Elixir of Immortality", "The Juice of Sapho"],
            "answer": "The Spice Melange"
        },
        {
            "question": "From which movie does the quote 'I've seen things you people wouldn't believe. Attack ships on fire off the shoulder of Orion. I watched c-beams glitter in the dark near the Tannh√§user Gate. All those moments will be lost in time, like tears in rain. Time to die.' come from?",
            "options": ["Blade Runner", "Star Wars", "The Matrix", "Interstellar"],
            "answer": "Blade Runner"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who are the Dune Navigators?",
            "options": [
                "Advanced humans who use the spice melange to navigate interstellar travel",
                "Interstellar space pilots",
                "Seafarers who explore the oceans in the world of Windward",
                "Time travelers in the world of Doctor Who"
            ],
            "answer": "Advanced humans who use the spice melange to navigate interstellar travel"
        }
    ]
}